{
  "APStats": [
    {
      "id": "Q1",
      "question": "Question1",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "dadffd",
        "blah",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q2",
      "question": "How does a positive outlier affect a dataset?",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "The median stays relatively the same, and the mean increases",
      "solution": "When adding a positive outlier, the value will shift slightly for the mean. This is because the mean is the average of a data set, and adding a higher value will shift the mean to include this higher value, causing the mean to increase. In comparison, the median only takes the number of each value into account, so the middle value does not change very much.",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "The mean and median increase.",
        "The median decreases, the mean stays relatively the same.",
        "The median stays relatively the same, and the mean increases.",
        "The mean and median stay the same."

      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q3",
      "question": "Question3",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Any difference between the sample results and the truth about the population that tends to occur in the same direction whenever using this sampling method",
      "solution": "During sampling, bias is created when results are skewed unevenly towards a specific population.",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Any difference between the sample result and the truth about the population.",        
        "The difference between the sample result and the truth about the population due to using chance to select a sample.",
        "Any difference between the sample results and the truth about the population due to practical difficulties such as contacting the subjects selected.",
        "Any difference between the sample results and the truth about the population that tends to occur in the same direction whenever using this sampling method."]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q4",
      "question": "Question4",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "II only",
      "solution": "As there was only around a third of the participants who responded to the survey, there is a large amount of the population that is unaccounted for. This is known non-response bias, which can skew the results of a survey because the opinions of the rest of the population is not known.",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "I only",
        "II only",
        "II and III only",
        "I, II, and III" 
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q5",
      "question": "Question5",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Randomized block, blocked by gender",
      "solution": "The subjects (men and women) are organized into different groups within their groups, which makes them blocked by gender. The participants are randomized, which makes it a randomized block. ",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Completely randomized with one factor, gender", 
        "Completely randomized with one factor, drug", 
        "Randomized block, blocked by drug and gender", 
        "Randomized block, blocked by gender"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q6",
      "question": "Question6",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "4.83 inches",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "4.83 inches",
        "8.93 inches",
        "5.18 inches",
        "The standard deviation cannot be computed from the given information"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q7",
      "question": "Question7",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "If A and B are independent, then they cannot be mutually exclusive ",
      "solution": " Independent events are events that can occur at the same time, but do not affect the outcome of each other. In comparison, mutually exclusive events are events that cannot occur simultaneously. Because of this, an event cannot be independent and mutually exclusive at the same time.",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "If A and B are mutually exclusive, then they must be independent",
        "If A and B are independent, then they must be mutually exclusive",
        "If A and B are not mutually exclusive, then they must be independent",
        "If A and B are independent, then they cannot be mutually exclusive "
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q8",
      "question": "Question8",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "0.035",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "0.011",
        "0.035",
        "0.092",
        "0.989" 
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q9",
      "question": "Question9",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "The number of digits I read in a randomly selected row of the random digits table until I find a 7",
      "solution": " For a geometric variable, an instance is repeated until it occurs. In this instance, the action (reading numbers) is repeated until the goal is reached (finding a 7) which makes it geometric.",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "The number of times I have to roll a die to get two 6s",
        "The number of cards I deal from a well-shuffled deck of 52 cards until I get a heart",
        "The number of digits I read in a randomly selected row of the random digits table until I find a 7",
        "The number of 7s in a row of 40 random digits"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q10",
      "question": "Question10",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "X = average amount of homework student does per night; Y = student’s height",
      "solution": " In statistics, the definition of independence is ‘two events that can occur at the same time, but do not affect each other/the probability of the other event occurring.’ Logically, a student’s height and the amount of homework a student has are two variables that can occur at the same time, but do not affect each other.",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "X = student’s height; Y = student’s weight",
        "X = student’s PSAT Math score; Y = PSAT Verbal score",
        "X = average amount of homework student does per night; Y = student’s GPA",
        "X = average amount of homework student does per night; Y = student’s height"        
      ]
    }
  ],
  "APCalc": [
    {
      "id": "Q1",
      "question": "cal1",
      "isImage": true,
      "answer": "-2/(√x)",
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "-2/(√x)",
        "-2",
        "1/(√x)",
        "2/(√x)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q2",
      "question": "bla2",
      "isImage": true,
      "answer": "335/3",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "335/6",
        "45",
        "5/3",
        "335/3"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q3",
      "question": "cal1",
      "isImage": true,
      "answer": "3(x^2)*cos(x^3)*log(x^2)+sin(x^3)*2/(x*ln(10))",
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "cos(x^3)* 1/(ln(10)*x^2)",
        "cos(x^3)*log(x^2)+1/(ln(10)*x^2)*sin(x^3)",
        "-cos(x^3)*log(x^2)+1/(ln(10)*x^2)*sin(x^3)",
        "3(x^2)*cos(x^3)*log(x^2)+sin(x^3)*2/(x*ln(10))"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q4",
      "question": "bla3",
      "isImage": true,
      "answer": "1/(2πr)",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "good",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1",
        "dadffdddd"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q5",
      "question": "cal1",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": 2,
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "NA",
        "bla",
        "good"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q6",
      "question": "cal1",
      "isImage": true,
      "answer": 2,
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla",
        "good",
        "NA"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q7",
      "question": "cal1",
      "isImage": true,
      "answer": 2,
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "NA",
        "bla",
        "good"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q8",
      "question": "cal1",
      "isImage": true,
      "answer": 2,
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla",
        "good",
        "NA"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q9",
      "question": "cal1",
      "isImage": true,
      "answer": 2,
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "NA",
        "badchoice2",
        "bla",
        "good"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q10",
      "question": "cal1",
      "isImage": true,
      "answer": 2,
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla",
        "NA",
        "good"
      ]
    }
  ],
  "Physics": [
    {
      "id": "Q1",
      "question": "How many centimeters are in one meter? ",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "100",
      "solution": "Conversion of length units",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "0.1",
        "10",
        "100",
        "1000"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q2",
      "question": "Which of the following is not a vector?",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Temperature",
      "solution": "You know, vectors, direction and magnitude",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Velocity",
        "300^i + 400^j",
        "Gravity",
        "Temperature"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q3",
      "question": "Projectile will attain its maximum range, if it is fired at an angle of ?",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "45",
      "solution": "If the downward acceleration is constant, the time of the object in the air is proportional to the horizontal distance",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "220",
        "57",
        "15",
        "45"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q4",
      "question": "Of these pairs, which is made up of two vectors?",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Velocity and force",
      "solution": "Vectors and scalars.",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "acceleration and electric charge",
        "mass and gravitational field",
        "Velocity and force",
        "speed and time interval"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q5",
      "question": "A man presses more weight on earth at:",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Standing position",
      "solution": "When the weight is certain, the smaller the area under pressure, the greater the pressure on the ground",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Sitting position",
        "Lying position",
        "Standing position",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q6",
      "question": "A piece of ice is dropped in a vessel containing kerosene. When ice melts, the level of kerosene will",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Fall",
      "solution": "Water is less dense than ice and all",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Fall",
        "Rise",
        "None of these",
        "Remain level"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q7",
      "question": "Young's modulus is the property of?",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Solid only",
      "solution": "young's modulus is only applicable to solids because of the deformation, ductility, stretching and resistance of the object. ",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Gas only",
        "Both Solid and Liquid",
        "Liquid only",
        "Solid only"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q8",
      "question": "An artificial Satellite revolves round the Earth in circular orbit, which quantity remains constant?",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Angular acceleration",
      "solution": "When in orbit, velocity, and other accelerations change, but angular acceleration is always the same",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Angular acceleration",
        "Linear velocity",
        "Angular displacement",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q9",
      "question": "The product of force and velocity is called?",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Power",
      "solution": "Power to the people! The means are in your hands!",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Work",
        "Energy",
        "Momentum",
        "Power"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q10",
      "question": "Which one of the following has the highest value of specific heat ?",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Water",
      "solution": "Properties of water",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Alcohol",
        "Methane",
        "Kerosene",
        "Water"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q11",
      "question": "With the increase of pressure, the boiling point of any substance:",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Increases",
      "solution": "The boiling point is proportional to the air pressure. The higher the air pressure, the higher the boiling point.",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Decreases",
        "Increases",
        "Remains same",
        "Zero"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q12",
      "question": "Electronegativity is the measure of",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "Non-metallic substance",
      "solution": "Electronegativity properties",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "Metallic character",
        "Basic Character",
        "Non-metallic substance",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "Q13",
      "question": "As defined in physics, work is?",
      "isImage": false,
      "answer": "A scalar quantity",
      "solution": "The concept of scalar quantity",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "A scalar quantity",
        "A vector quantity",
        "What you do for a job",
        "Always positive"
      ]
    }
  ]
}